[{"answer": " Hi Suzanne. Whats new", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Well, I have some exciting news.  Were finally going to adopt a baby", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Hi Suzanne. Whats new", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": "How wonderful. That is such great news.  So, give me the update", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Well, I have some exciting news.  Were finally going to adopt a baby", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Well, you know we have one child of our own, Molly, and David and I decide", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 15, "question": "How wonderful. That is such great news.  So, give me the update", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " I remember.  That was quite a while ago", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Well, you know we have one child of our own, Molly, and David and I decide", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " That was just the beginning. The application process has been very long an", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 21, "question": " I remember.  That was quite a while ago", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " I can imagine. I guess the adoption agency wants to make sure all the babies g", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 23, "question": " That was just the beginning. The application process has been very long an", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Yeah, and thats a good thing.  But, the waiting list was three years for ", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 32, "question": " I can imagine. I guess the adoption agency wants to make sure all the babies g", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Its a serious decision to make", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Yeah, and thats a good thing.  But, the waiting list was three years for ", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " I know, I know.  David and I talked a lot about it, and now we have finall", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Its a serious decision to make", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Thats great", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 42, "question": " I know, I know.  David and I talked a lot about it, and now we have finall", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Yeah, were so excited", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Thats great", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Have you talked about it with Molly yet? How old is she now?  Five", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Yeah, were so excited", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Molly is four now and weve talked with her about it. She doesnt reall", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Have you talked about it with Molly yet? How old is she now?  Five", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " How does she like the idea of a new baby", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Molly is four now and weve talked with her about it. She doesnt reall", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " She is excited about having a little baby sister.  She wants to share her roo", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 50, "question": " How does she like the idea of a new baby", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Thats great that Mollys excited about a new sister.  So, why did you choos", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 55, "question": " She is excited about having a little baby sister.  She wants to share her roo", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Well, there are many children in Guatemala that are up for adoption", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Thats great that Mollys excited about a new sister.  So, why did you choos", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Really?  I didnt know that.  Whats the process like adopting from that country", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Well, there are many children in Guatemala that are up for adoption", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " We had to submit income tax forms from the last 3 years. We also ha", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Really?  I didnt know that.  Whats the process like adopting from that country", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Did they have to come to your house", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 65, "question": " We had to submit income tax forms from the last 3 years. We also ha", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Oh yes, they came a few times, and at different times of the day. The", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Did they have to come to your house", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " You must have been a little nervous about those meetings, huh", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Oh yes, they came a few times, and at different times of the day. The", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Kind of.  Oh, they also do a criminal check on you and you have to do ", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 72, "question": " You must have been a little nervous about those meetings, huh", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Id hope so.  You dont have to worry about that though", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Kind of.  Oh, they also do a criminal check on you and you have to do ", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " No.  So, now we are just weeks away from traveling to Guatemala to pick u", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Id hope so.  You dont have to worry about that though", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " It sounds like there are a lot of hoops to jump through, but it will be worth it i", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 83, "question": " No.  So, now we are just weeks away from traveling to Guatemala to pick u", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " I know.  Once we have the new baby, well forget about all these years wev", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 89, "question": " It sounds like there are a lot of hoops to jump through, but it will be worth it i", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Well, I am very, very happy for you. Let me know if I can do anything for yo", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 91, "question": " I know.  Once we have the new baby, well forget about all these years wev", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Thank you.  That is so nice of you to offer", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Well, I am very, very happy for you. Let me know if I can do anything for yo", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Of course.  What are friends for", "docId": "07-02", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Thank you.  That is so nice of you to offer", "qSentId": 97}]
